<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Yongchao Ma</title><link>https://yongchaoma.com/</link><description>Recent content on Yongchao Ma</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://yongchaoma.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Research Projects</title><link>https://yongchaoma.com/research/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2020 17:06:22 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://yongchaoma.com/research/</guid><description>Optimal Stratification in Bayesian Adaptive Survey Designs Statistics Netherlands
Collecting official statistics survey data is getting more difficult. Costs have been increasing while budgets have been decreasing. The deteriorating response rates also yield nonresponse bias that jeopardizes the validity of inferences from data. Adaptive survey designs are based on the rationale that any population is heterogeneous in both: its response and answers to surveys and its costs to be recruited and interviewed.</description></item><item><title>Publications</title><link>https://yongchaoma.com/pubs/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2020 12:25:33 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://yongchaoma.com/pubs/</guid><description>Journal Articles van de Schoot, R., de Bruin, J., Schram, R., Zahedi, P., de Boer, J., Weijdema, F., Kramer, B., Huijts, M., Hoogerwerf, M., Ferdinands, G., Harkema, A., Willemsen, J., Ma, Y., Fang, Q., Hindriks, S., Tummers, L., &amp;amp; Oberski, D. L. (2021). An open source machine learning framework for efficient and transparent systematic reviews. Nature Machine Intelligence, 3(2), 125-133. Presentations Ma, Y., 2016. The Change of the Sociopolitical Attitudes of the Middle Class in China: 2003–2013.</description></item><item><title>About me</title><link>https://yongchaoma.com/about/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2020 11:31:38 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://yongchaoma.com/about/</guid><description>I am a research master student and research assistant in the Department of Methodology and Statistics at Utrecht University. I am also an intern at Statistics Netherlands.
I received my Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s degree in Sociology from China in 2017 and my Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in Criminology and Criminal Justice from the University of Macau in 2019, including a one-semester exchange program at Linköping University in Sweden.
My research interests focus on adaptive survey design, survey nonresponse, quantitative methods, inequality &amp;amp; stratification.</description></item></channel></rss>