<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Research Projects on Yongchao Ma</title>
    <link>https://yongchaoma.com/research/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Research Projects on Yongchao Ma</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2020 17:06:22 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://yongchaoma.com/research/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Optimal Stratification in Bayesian Adaptive Survey Designs</title>
      <link>https://yongchaoma.com/research/survey/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yongchaoma.com/research/survey/</guid>
      <description>Statistics Netherlands
Collecting official statistics survey data is getting more difficult. Costs have been increasing while budgets have been decreasing. Declining response rates yield nonresponse bias that jeopardizes the validity of inferences from data. As a result, statistical institutes are interested in adaptive survey designs that can balance cost and data quality. Analogous to the group sequential designs in clinical trials, adaptive survey designs are based on the rationale that different data collection strategies may be effective for different members of the population.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Asreview: Active learning for Systematic Reviews</title>
      <link>https://yongchaoma.com/research/asreview/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://yongchaoma.com/research/asreview/</guid>
      <description>Utrecht University
Systematic reviews are “top of the bill” in research. The Active learning for Systematic Reviews (ASReview) project, publised in Nature Machine Intelligence, implements machine learning algorithms to accelerate the step of screening abstracts and titles with a minimum of papers to be read by a human with no or very few false negatives.
As a research assistant under the supervision of Prof. Dr. Rens van de Schoot, my task involves:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
